And I boarded the plane in a really good
mood. And the flight attendants ON
SPIRIT, THEY'RE NOT NICE.
NO, THEY'RE NOT NICE. I BOARDED THE
PLANE, I WAS LIKE THIS, "GOOD MORNING."
SHE WAS LIKE, "SIT DOWN." I WENT, "OH,
OKAY, RIGHT."
SO, I'M ON A COMPUTER GOOGLING flights
from New Jersey to Utah, and all of a
sudden, you know,
the pop-up ads, all of a sudden out of
nowhere,
"Spirit Airlines, $9."
>> [laughter]
>> So,
I DIDN'T WANT TO FLY SPIRIT. SO, I
CLICKED THE BOX. SO, I re-Googled it.
Hey,
"SPIRIT AIRLINES, $9. Fly wherever you
want to go around the world, round trip,
$9."
>> [laughter]
>> "CLICK HERE." SO, I CLICKED. I CLICKED
IT, AND IT SAID, "CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU'RE THE 100TH CLICKER." Fireworks are
going off, confetti, the whole bit,
right? "Please call this number within
the next 30 minutes, 1-800-Spirit." So,
I call 1-800-Spirit, and I get this.
"Thank you for calling Spirit Airlines.
This is Diane. May I help you?" And I'm
thinking, "Wow, $9, and she speaks
English. So far,
this is good. This is good so far,
right?"
I'm a gentleman.
"Hello, Diane. My name is Jeff Norris,
and I don't mean to brag or anything,
but uh
I was THE 100TH CLICKER."
"HEY, HEY, I WAS THE 100TH CLICKER."
"WELL, I'm glad you told me, Jeff,
because this flight for you from to to
Utah is only going to cost you $9." And
I was so excited cuz I I have 10 bucks
IN CHECKING.
SO,
I SAID, "DIANE, LET'S BOOK THE FLIGHT."
SO, we book it, and we're talking. I go,
"Diane, do I understand you correctly?
You mean to tell me from New Jersey to
Utah is only going to cost me $4.50
and then coming home is another $4.50
$9.00 That's it, $9.00 I just need your
credit card.
So, I gave it to her.
Yeah, now you tell me.
>> [laughter]
>> SO, I GAVE IT TO HER. SHE GOES, "JEFF,
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE I CAN DO FOR
YOU?" And I I said, "Diane, all right,
you know, while I have you on the phone,
I'll be checking two bags." She goes,
"Oh,
oh, you're bringing a bag?"
>> [laughter]
>> Uh hold on a minute, Jeff. That's an
extra $185.
FOR YOUR BAG. Oh my goodness, Diane.
Well,
can I pick my seat?
Oh, YOU WANT TO SIT? UH HOLD ON, JEFF.
THERE'S NO $9.00. I'M UP TO LIKE $472
NOW.
>> [laughter]
>> I'M THINKING, if I'm spending this much
money,
I want to fly first class. I never flew
first class in my life.
And I'm thinking for this money, I'm
going to fly. So, I said, "Diane, I'd
like to buy a first class ticket." So,
she goes, "Jeff, I'm sorry, we don't
have first class on Spirit."
And then she asked me a question that I
honestly did not know how to answer.
She says, "We don't have first class,
Jeff, but
would you like a big seat?"
>> [laughter]
>> The last time somebody asked me that
question, I was 9 years old at the
THANKSGIVING TABLE.
YES. YES. AND MY AUNT DIED AND I GOT
promoted to the big seat.
That's big seat to me. Right?
I DON'T KNOW.
SO, I SAID, "YES, GIVE ME THE BIG SEAT."
SO, THAT'S THE BIG SHOT. THAT'S seat 1A.
So, I I was so excited to come here. I
really was. I Cuz laughter is my
favorite sound. It really is. It's my
favorite song in the world. So, like I
love you guys. The energy in the room.
And I was so excited to come out here
and it's an honor to be on this stage.
And I boarded the plane in a really good
mood. And the flight attendants ON
SPIRIT, THEY'RE NOT NICE.
>> [laughter]
>> NO, THEY'RE NOT NICE. I BOARDED THE
PLANE. I WAS LIKE THIS, "GOOD MORNING."
SHE WAS LIKE, "SIT DOWN." I WENT, "OH,
OKAY."
>> [laughter]
>> SO, LET'S SEE IF I CAN REENACT MY TRIP
from Jersey to here. Okay. The Yeah. The
big seat. OKAY.
THIS HERE
>> [laughter]
>> IS THE BIG SEAT ON SPIRIT AIRLINES,
OKAY?
>> [laughter]
>> THIS HERE IS THE WALL. That's about it,
right like that.
>> [laughter]
>> So, I go to board the plane and I can't
like and you know, people are behind
you. You get that nervous feeling.
People are like, "Come on, sit down
already." I'm like, "I I can't get in,
you know." You You can't I I can't I'm
trying to get in. I'm going like that.
And I I don't know how you get in the
seat. And the flight attendant, she's
embarrassing me. SHE GOES, "SIR,
SIR, WOULD YOU PLEASE TAKE YOUR SEAT?
YOU'RE DELAYING THE BOARDING PROCESS."
I'M LIKE, "I'M TRYING, YOU SKY BULLY.
STOP PICKING ON ME, RIGHT?"
"PREPARE FOR TAKEOFF, OKAY? PREPARE FOR
TAKEOFF." THE COMPANY YOU HOP, OKAY.
"Prepare for takeoff, Spirit Airlines."
Okay, prepare for takeoff.
Okay, takeoff.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay,
now just
takeoff.
Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> How long is this flight? 5 and 1/2
hours, right?
>> [laughter]
>> What you worry once we're in the air you
can put your chair back and recline. I
go that's going to be fantastic.
We're in you can put your chair back.
Okay, just pull this button. Okay,
click. Oh, that's great.
Much better now.
I'll sleep for hours, right?
>> [laughter]
>> I sit next to somebody. This is me.
Hello, good morning. Good evening. How
are you? My name My name is Jeff. I'll
even introduce myself.
It doesn't ask.
No need for an interview.
>> [laughter]
>> Where you from? Jersey.
Oh, I'm I'm I'm Bob. I'm Jeff. Nice to
meet you.
So, uh what do you do for a living?
>> [laughter]
>> Believe it not,
I'm a comedian. No way. Really? Tell me
a joke.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, please don't do this. It's a
five and a five and a half-hour flight.
What do you do for a living? Oh, I'm an
accountant. Really? Do my taxes. Before
we
we get there, huh?
>> [laughter]
>> So, we're on the plane, Spirit Airlines.
We're in the air
for like 15 minutes.
The plane starts making all these weird
noises, right?
So, I get I get a little nervous on a
plane. I do. So, you know what I do if I
get nervous? I'm not I'm not ashamed to
admit it.
I say a little prayer
in my head. In any situation in life, I
say a little prayer
in my head. I'm not the holiest guy, but
I do believe in the power of prayer, you
know?
And I think no matter what your faith is
or no matter who you fly with, everybody
>> [laughter]
>> everybody says a little prayer
before takeoff.
But on Spirit,
it's mandatory. YES!
YES! IT'S ON THE BACK OF THE RECEIPT.
IT SAYS, "PLEASE PRAY SO WE can leave."
That's why they CALL IT SPIRIT.
>> [applause]
>> THAT'S NOT THE NAME OF THE AIRLINE, IT'S
AN ACRONYM.
YEAH, it means start praying and runway,
it'll take off.
That's what Spirit means on the Did you
realize that?
>> [music]